

ERNALD T. BAUTISTA

SALES AREA MANAGER (CSC-Professional Eligible)

PERSONAL PROFILE

Performance-oriented Sales Leader offering exceptional record of achievement over 6 year career. Tenacious manager with strategic and analytical approach to solving problems, bringing in customers and accomplishing profit targets. Talented in identifying and capitalizing on emerging market trends and revenue opportunities.

SKILLS

- Servant Leader
- Problem Solving
- · Communications abilities
- Resilience
- Data Analytics
- People Management Public Relation

CONTACTINFORMATION

Address: Blk 8 Lot 27 Sto Tomas Street Fiesta Community San Rafael Tarlac City. Mobile Number: 0977-819-8556/0976-172-6162

Email Address: ernaldbautista@yahoo.com.ph

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Tarlac State University

Bachelor of Science in Hotel and Restaurant Management (2010-2014)

• 2014 Academic Excellence Awardee

Tarlac National High School (2006-2010)

Tibag Elementary School (2000-2006))

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sales Area Manager

Leslie Corporation(Minute Burger) I May 2022 - present Area Coverage: Central Luzon Immediate Superior: Regional Manager

The SAM is a leadership role, responsible for the overall revenue generation and operational efficiency of the trade area.

Franchise Dev't Officer (Area Manager)

Shawarma Shack Fast-food Corp. I July 2021 - May 2022 Area Coverage: Region 1,2,CAR & Tarlac Immediate Superior: Head, Franchise and Business Development

The AM is a leadership role, responsible for the overall revenue generation, business development and operational efficiency of the trade area.

Sales and Marketing Manager

FonteFresca Foods Inc by Brookside Group of Companies I January 2019 - July 2020
Area Coverage: Metro Manila and NCR
JImmediate Superior: VP for Sales and Marketing

The SMM is a leadership role, responsible for the overall revenue generation, business development, distribution and marketing of the trade area.

Business Development Supervisor

Personal Collection Direct Selling Inc I November 2015 - January 2019

Area Coverage: Pampanga

Immediate Superior: Area Business Development Manager
The BDS is a leadership role, responsible for the
overall revenue generation, business development,
recruitment and training of the assign area.

Shift Manager

Scotland Inc I April 2015 - November 2015

The SM is a leadership role, responsible for the overall revenue generation and operational efficiency of the assign outlet.

Management Trainee to Store Manager

Performance Foods Corporation I April 2014- April 2015

The SM is a leadership role, responsible for the overall revenue generation and operational efficiency of the assign outlet.